嘿 二吨 看着卡车
Hey, Two Ton, watch the truck.
我们可不希望我们偷来的钱被偷了
We wouldn't want somebody to steal our stolen money.
哈哈
Ha ha.
嘿 这里禁止停车
Hey, this is a no-parking zone.
这是你的罚单
Here's your ticket,
这是你的罚款
and here's your fine.
干得漂亮 米奇
Nice work, Mikey.
咳 忍者的基本操作而已
Eh, it's a ninja thing.
现在 咱们把拉斐救出来
Now let's get Raph out of there.
唉 没人用经典的老式挂锁了吗
Man, whatever happened to good old-fashioned padlocks?
嘿 那还有什么挑战性呢
Heh. Where's the fun in that?
这个交给我了
This one's all mine.
你说什么 拉斐尔
What's that, Raphael?
你得大声点 老兄
You're gonna have to speak up, dude.
我听不见
I can't hear you.
好的 这我听到了
Okay, I heard that.
我正试着工作呢
I'm trying to work here.
嘿 拉夫
Hey, Raph.
欢迎回来 兄弟
Welcome back, bro!
真是个暴脾气
What a hothead.
嗷 嗷 嗷 嗷 嗷 嗷 嗷!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Ow!
呃 拉夫
Uh, Raph?
没时间胡闹了
We don't have time for this.
为什么呢
And why not?
因为这里不止有我们
Because we're not alone.
看看这些怪胎
Look at the freaks.
穿的什么蠢服装
What's with the dweeby costumes?
又不是万圣节
This ain't Halloween.
你们完蛋了 怪胎
You're going down, freaks!
没人敢招惹紫龙帮
Nobody messes with The Purple Dragons,
尤其是穿着龟服的蠢货
especially wearing stupid turtle costumes!
咱们快离开这里
Let's get outta here!
等等我
I'm with you!
快走 快走 快走
Go, go, go!
给我点绿色
Gimme some green!
嘿 这比预想的要简单
Well, that was easier than expected.
希望再多来几个这样的家伙
I hope there are more of those guys.
我才刚热了个身呢
I'm just getting warmed up.
呃 好吧
Uh, well,
看来你如愿以偿了 拉斐小子
looks like you got your wish, Raphie boy.
那些家伙是忍者吗
Are those guys ninjas?
嗯 他们确实有忍者风范
Well, they're certainly ninja-esque.
做好应对一切的准备
Be ready for anything.
我肯定会很享受这个的
I am so gonna enjoy this.
不错的龙踢腿
Nice dragon kick.
啊 漂亮的凤凰拳
Ah, sweet double phoenix punch.
嘿 知道这招吗
Hey, you know this one?
多尼 是我们在打他们
Don, are we beating them,
还是他们在打我们
or are they beating us?
等我们赢的时候再来问我 米奇
Ask me again when we're winning, Mikey.
是啊 和我想的一样
Yeah, that's what I thought.